Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- District Office Files, ca. 1934, 1948, 1953, 1963-90; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  Miscellaneous Files, ca. 1934, 1948, 1953, and 1963-1985, contain primarily materials from the Congressman's congressional career but a few items pre-date 1963. Included are files documenting grant funding for projects such as the LA freeways; the political campaigns of Congressman Hawkins and other democrats; and the work of former district office aides Charles Knox, Bob Wilson, and Adam Burton. Also included are certificates and awards presented to the Congressman. In Box 67 are oversize photos and miscellaneous materials. The Miscellaneous Files are unorganized.
  Finally, there are CCEDE (Coordinating Council on Economic Development and Employment) Files from 1963 to 1972. During this period Charles Knox, Congressman Hawkins' district office manager, served as a consultant to the council. Congressman Hawkins founded the CCEDE around 1961 to provide answers to many of the social problems of south, central Los Angeles.
  - Bill Files, 88th-93th Congresses, (1963-74)
    - Federal Aviation. (Box 46)
    - Atomic Energy. (Box 46)
    - Air Pollution. (Box 46)
    - H.R. 13622, Library Services and Construction Act Amendment of, 1966. (Box 46)
    - H.R. 15904, The Mexican American Rural Community Anti-Poverty Act of, 1975. (Box 46)
    - Agriculture. (Box 46)
    - Administration. (Box 46)
    - Banking and Currency. (Box 46)
    - Capitol House Dining Room. (Box 46)
    - Child Abuse Act. (Box 46)
    - Child Nutrition Act. (Box 46)
    - Citizens of the United States. (Box 46)
    - Colorado River. (Box 46)
    - Consumer Affairs. (Box 46)
    - Contract Work Hour Standard. (Box 46)
    - Damage and Property Loss. (Box 46)
    - District of Columbia. (Box 46)
    - Armed Services. (Box 46)
    - Afro-American History and Culture. (Box 46)
    - H.R. 9927, D.C. Self-Government/Government Reorganization. (Box 46)
    - Emergency Detention Camps. (Box 46)
    - Entertainment. (Box 46)
    - Equal Rights for Men and Women. (Box 46)
    - Ethics. (Box 46)
    - Family Planning. (Box 46)
    - Federal Financial Assistance. (Box 46)
    - Foreign Affairs. (Box 46)
    - Education. (Box 46)
    - Employment. (Box 46)
    - Health. (Box 46)
    - Housing. (Box 46)
    - Hunger Commission. (Box 46)
    - Immigration. (Box 46)
    - Insurance. (Box 46)
    - Internal Revenue. (Box 46)
    - International Conflict. (Box 46)
    - Internal Security. (Box 46)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs. (Box 46)
    - Iron and Steel Orderly Trade Act. (Box 46)
    - Job Corps. (Box 46)
    - Judiciary. (Box 46)
    - Juvenile Delinquency. (Box 46)
    - Labor. (Box 46)
    - Library Services. (Box 46)
    - Maritime Academy. (Box 46)
    - Martin Luther King Day. (Box 46)
    - Mental Health Centers Act. (Box 46)
    - Middle East War. (Box 46)
    - Military Services. (Box 46)
    - Misconduct by U.S. Troops. (Box 46)
    - Narcotics. (Box 46)
    - National Economic Conversion Commission. (Box 46)
    - National Foundation on the Arts. (Box 46)
    - National Park Services. (Box 46)
    - Older American Act. (Box 46)
    - Office of Defense Review. (Box 46)
    - Overseas Teachers Pay. (Box 46)
    - Pop Warner Little Scholars, Inc. (Box 46)
    - Post Office. (Box 46)
    - Prisoners of War. (Box 46)
    - Public Works Resident. (Box 46)
    - Commissioner Committee on Rules. (Box 46)
    - Selective Service. (Box 46)
    - Small Business Act. (Box 46)
    - Social Security. (Box 46)
    - State of California. (Box 46)
    - Textile Articles. (Box 46)
    - United States and Mexico. (Box 46)
    - Urban Mass Transportation. (Box 46)
    - Truth in Lending Act. (Box 46)
    - Veterans Administration. (Box 46)
    - Residency Voting Act. (Box 46)
    - Working Conditions. (Box 46)
    - Workers Compensation. (Box 46)
    - Department of Youth Affairs. (Box 46)
  - Bill Files, 88th-94th Congresses, 1963-76
    - Agriculture
      - H.R. 8578, To Amend the Community Service Act, 1974. (Box 46)
    - Area Development
      - H.R. 5203, Los Angeles Area Redevelopment Act. (Box 46)
    - Civil Rights
      - H.R. 2516, Violence or Intimidation Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4952, To Amend Civil Rights Act, 1964. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 7152, Civil Rights Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6333, Act Against Discrimination. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6332, To Protect Constitutional Rights of Individuals. (Box 46)
    - Consumer
      - H.R. 17486, To Provide For Orderly Trade in Textile Articles and Articles of Leather Footwear, etc. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 2336, Consumer Protection Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
    - Economic Opportunity
      - H.R. 7265, Domestic Volunteer Service Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
      - P.L. 90-222, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1967. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10351, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1971. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10440, Economic Opportunity Act, 1964. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 12464, Economic Opportunity Amendments. (Box 46)
    - Education
      - H.R. 445, Title I Elementary/ Secondary Education Act of, 1965. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 3081, Comprehensive Child Development Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 1083, Comprehensive Child Development Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 1769, Children With Specific Learning Disabilities. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5823, Better Schools Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5163, Educationally Disadvantaged, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4056, Comprehensive Child Development, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10943, Higher Education Act of, 1965. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9658, National Teacher Fellowship Act of, 1965. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9636, To Amend National School Lunch. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6636, Teachers' Sabbatical Leave Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4030, School Children's Assistance Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6327, Public School Desegregation Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 8382, Vocational Education Amendment of, 1967. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 15066, Partnership for Learning and Earning Act of, 1968. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9631, Teacher Sabbatical Leave Program. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 13400, Insured Student Loans. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9627, National Teacher Fellowship Act, 1965. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5542, Adult Basic Education Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10224, National Student Loan, Incorporated Act, 1964. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4955, Vocational Education Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 16461, Vocational Education Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 8527, To Amend the Vocational Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 14910, The Ethnic Heritage Studies Center. (Box 46)
    - Employment
      - H.R. 50, Equal Opportunity and Full Employment Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 8420, Public Service Employment, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10714, Employee Benefit Security Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 2858, Employee Benefit Security Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 1, Youth Employment Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - Hatch Political Activities Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 13743, Fair Labor Standards Amendments, 1966. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4031, Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4032, Equal Pay Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 1890 and H.R. 5131, Youth Employment Act (2). (Box 46)
      - H.R. 680, The Equal Employment Opportunities Act, 1967. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9232, To Prohibit Discrimination in Employment Because of Race, Color, or Creed. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 719, Federal Employees Compensation Programs. (Box 46)
    - Foreign Affairs
      - House of Congress Res. 269. (Box 46)
      - H.Res. 785, Majority Rule for People of Rhodesia, 1967. (Box 46)
      - House of Congress Res. 151. (Box 46)
    - Housing and Urban Development
      - H.R. 9559, To Amend National Housing Act. (Box 46)
      - P.L. 89-117, Housing and Urban Development Act of, 1965. (Box 46)
      - H.Res. 13622, Library Services and Construction Act, 1966. (Box 46)
    - Humanities and Art
      - H.R. 368, National Humanities Foundation Act, 1965. (Box 46)
    - Immigration
      - H.R. 8188, Immigration Nationality Act Amendment. (Box 46)
    - Internal Revenue
      - H.R. 5227, Southwest Hospital Foundation Relief. (Box 46)
      - Tax Reform Act, 1969. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 1041, Tax Equity Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 17331, Income Maintenance Program. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4266. (Box 46)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs
      - H.R. 4691, Lower Colorado River Basin Project Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 11370, Pacific Southwest Project. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 10392, Winter Recreation at San Gorgonio Wilderness Area. (Box 46)
    - Judiciary
      - H.R. 12771, Uniform Holiday. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6331. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6288. (Box 46)
      - H.J.Res. 1053. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6145, National Institute of Criminal Justice. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 7824, Legal Services Corporation Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9525, National Legal Services Corporation Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 757, To Designate Birthday of Martin Luther King, Jr. as Holiday. (Box 46)
    - Manpower Development Training Act
      - H.R. 11570, MDTA. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5205, To Amend MDTA of, 1962. (Box 46)
    - Military
      - H.R. 12326. (Box 46)
    - Public Welfare
      - H.R. 2966, Child and Family Services. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6267, Problems of Juvenile Delinquency. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 42, Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 8597, Public Health Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6729, Welfare Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 16359, Public Health Service Act, 1970. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5204, U.S. Commission on Aging Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6330, Amendments to Hospital Survey and Construction Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6329, To Amend the Public Service Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 6858, Federal Financial Assistance to Family Planning Program. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 9743. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4878, Solid Waste Disposal Act. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 7265, Domestic Volunteer Service Act of, 1973. (Box 46)
    - Public Works and Economic Development
      - H.R. 11188, Public Works and Economic Development Act of, 1965. (Box 46)
    - Social Security
      - H.R. 2713. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 4580, Older Americans Act Amendments of 1969. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5266, Social Security Insurance Act of, 1963. (Box 46)
    - Veterans
      - H.R. 3953, To Amend U.S. Code, re Veterans. (Box 46)
      - H.R. 5202, To Amend U.S. Code. (Box 46)
  - Bill Files, 88th Congress, (1963-64)
    - H.R. 11377, Economic Opportunity. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 10440, Economic Opportunity. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 11370, Interior. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5542, Adult Basic Education Act of, 1963. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4955, Vocational Education. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 7771, Racial Discrimination. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 9559, National Housing. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 9846, National Defense Education Act of, 1964. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 7156, Construction and Maintenance, Public Schools. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 7237, Public School Desegregation Assistance Act. (Box 47)
    - H.J.Res. 1053, Judiciary. (Box 47)
    - H.Res. 690, Freedom of Religion. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4279, Library Services. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 405, Equal Employment Opportunity Act of, 1963. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 3001, National Education Improvement. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 10224, National Student Loan Insurance. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 7957, Older American Act of, 1963. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 8720, Manpower Development and Training Act of, 1962. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5202, Manpower Development and Training Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 1, Youth Employment Act of, 1963. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 1890, Youth Conservation Corps Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5131, Youth Employment Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 3000, National Education Improvement Act of, 1963. (Box 47)
  - Bill File, 92nd Congress (), 1971-72
    - H.R. 6069, Domestic Film Production Incentive Act of, 1971. (Box 47)
  - Bill Files, 93rd Congress (1973-74)
    - H.R. 16459, Equal Opportunity and Full Employment Act of, 1976. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 692, Resolution to Impeach Richard M. Nixon. (Box 47)
    - H.J.Res. 897, Resolution to Proclaim National Health Week. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2205, Public Service Employment Act of, 1975. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5535, Bill of Rights for the Mentally Retarded. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 8556, Minority Business Assistance Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 8953, U.S. Postal Services Arbitration Board. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 9927, District of Columbia Self-Government and Governmental Reorganization. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 11169, Social Services Amendments of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 11998, Follow Through Program. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 12464, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1974. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 14094, Development, Volunteer, and Other Community Assistance Programs Act of, 1974. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2858, Employee Benefit Security Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2966, Family and Child Services Act, 1975. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 10865, Community Services Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 10864, Extend Headstart Program. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 9422, Community Land Grant Act of (Treaty of Guadalupe-Hidalgo)., 1971 (Box 47)
    - H.R. 10714, Employee Benefit Security Act SubCommittee Hearings on Economic Opportunity Act, (2)., April and May 1971 (Box 47)
    - H.R. 12378, Energy Information Act. (Box 47)
    - P.L. 93-644, Community Services Act of, 1974. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2413, Consumer Protection Agency Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.Con.Res. 175. (Box 47)
    - H.Con.Res. 174. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2334 and H.R. 3985, Urban Recreational Opportunities Act of, Education (2)., 1973 (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2336, Consumer Protection Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 3277, Federal Trade Commission Act (Area Development). (Box 47)
    - H.R. 3984, H.R. 3986, H.R. 3987, Public Service Employment Act of (3)., 1973 (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4056, Comprehensive Child Development Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4522, Compensation for Work Injuries, Federal Employees. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4523, Community Land Grant Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4524, President's Action re Impoundment of Funds. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4230, Opportunities Industrialization Assistance Act, Education. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4382, Brownsville Raid Veterans. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4953, Community Land Grant Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4981, Community School Center Development Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5206, Foreign Trade and Investment Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 9298, Runaway Youth Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5203, National Science Policy and Priorities Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5230, Community Land Grant Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5478, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5706, H.R. 5707, Opportunities Industrialization Assistance Act (2). (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5852, Weather Modification Regulation Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6161, Employment and Inflation Act of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6316, Federal Disaster Insurance Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6566, Economic Opportunity Amendments of, 1973. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6783, Opportunities Industrialization Assistance Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2713, To Amend Title II and XVIII of Social Security Act. (Box 47)
    - Crime Insurance Act Information. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 15276, Juvenile Delinquency Prevention Act of, 1974. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 2302, Comprehensive Older Americans Services Amendments of, 1973. (Box 47)
  - Bill File, 97th Congress, (1981-82)
    - P.L. 97-300, Job Training Partnership Act, October 1982. (Box 47)
  - Bill Files, 98th Congress, (1983-84)
    - H.J.Res. 2, Nuclear Freeze. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 3112, Voting Rights Affirmative Action. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6576, Amends Age Discrimination in Employment. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 5369, Veterans Funeral Expenses. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 4785, Amends Older Americans Act of, 1965. (Box 47)
    - Vocational Education Act. (Box 47)
    - National Engineering and Science Report. (Box 47)
  - Bill File, 99th Congress, (1985-86)
    - H.R. 4300, Parental Leave. (Box 47)
  - Bill Files, 100th Congress, (1987-88)
    - H.R. 5, School Improvement Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 6, Effective Schools/Even Start. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 16, H.R. 30, Fair Work Opportunities (2). (Box 47)
    - H.R. 40, Community Renewal Employment. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 90, Education and Training for American Competitiveness. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 950, Special Education Needs Act, 1987. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 1398, Homeless Initiative. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 1755, Bilingual Education Improvement Act. (Box 47)
    - H.R. 1834, Minimum Wage Restoration Act, 1987. (Box 47)
  - Alphabetical Files
    - A-L, 1973. (Box 48)
    - M-Z, 1973. (Box 48)
    - A-Z, 1973. (Box 48)
    - A-Z, 1977. (Box 48)
    - A-Z, 1978. (Box 48)
    - A-Y, 1979. (Box 48)
    - A-Z, 1980. (Box 49)
    - A-Z, 1981. (Box 49)
    - A-Y, 1982. (Box 49)
    - A-Y, 1983. (Box 49)
    - A-W, 1984. (Box 49)
    - A-V, 1985. (Box 49)
    - A-W, 1986. (Box 49)
    - A-Z, 1987. (Box 49)
    - A-W, 1988. (Box 49)
  - Subject Files, 1963-75
    - Administration, Memos to Mr. Hawkins from C. Knox. (Box 91)
    - Agriculture
      - General Correspondence. (Box 91)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 91)
    - Anti-Poverty
      - Programs, Miscellaneous. (Box 91)
      - Questionnaire Responses, 1965. (Box 91)
      - Upward Bound Program. (Box 91)
    - Appropriations, Controversial Document, Thoms and Gibson-Synder. (Box 91)
    - Armed Services
      - Air Force Department. (Box 91)
      - Amnesty. (Box 91)
      - Army Department. (Box 91)
      - Camp Pendleton, Marine Corps. (Box 91)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 91)
      - Material on Military Grievance. (Box 91)
      - Navy Department. (Box 91)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 91)
      - Selective Service. (Box 91)
      - Weapons, Anti-Missile Base in Compton, California. (Box 91)
    - Banking and Currency
      - Minority Banks, Deposit Expansion Program. (Box 91)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 91)
    - Cannon, J. Alfred, M.D. (Box 91)
    - Civil Disorders, Watts Riots, 1965. (Box 91)
    - Civil Rights
      - Affirmative Action Programs. (Box 91)
      - Black Educator, The End of the Black Educator in the South by B.M. and J.W. Smith. (Box 91)
      - Commission on Civil Rights. (Box 91)
      - Commission on Equal Employment Opportunity. (Box 91)
      - Schools, Desegregation and Integration. (Box 91)
      - Equal Employment. (Box 91)
      - Equal Employment Newsclippings. (Box 91)
      - Office of Federal Contract Compliance (OFCC). (Box 91)
      - President's Commission on Equal Employment Opportunity, Olin-Mathieson Plant, Louisiana. (Box 91)
      - Various Newsclippings. (Box 91)
      - Voting, Racial Discrimination in Voting Women's Educational Equity Act of (H.R. 208)., 1973 (Box 91)
      - White House Conference. (Box 91)
    - Civil Service, General. (Box 91)
    - Commerce
      - General. (Box 91)
      - Census Bureau, Population of Congressional Districts., 1970 (Box 91)
      - Economic Development Administration (EDA). (Box 91)
      - Foreign Trade. (Box 91)
      - Office of Minority Business Enterprise (OMBE). (Box 91)
      - Watts Imperial Industrial Park. (Box 91)
    - Congress
      - Congressman Hawkin's Certificates of Election. (Box 91)
      - Legislative Correspondence, Miscellaneous. (Box 91)
      - Congressman William L. Dawson. (Box 91)
      - Reapportionment, California. (Box 91)
      - WIN Campaign Newsletter. (Box 91)
    - Congress, Congressional Black Caucus
      - General. (Box 91)
      - Alert Sheets. (Box 91)
      - Caucus Dinners. (Box 91)
      - Third Annual Caucus Dinner, September 1973. (Box 91)
      - Caucus Dinner,, Ossie Davis, Keynote Speaker., June 1971 (Box 91)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 91)
      - Caucus Meetings. (Box 92)
      - Oberlin, Black Caucus Referral Program. (Box 92)
      - Press Releases and Newsclippings. (Box 92)
      - Report to the Nation, May 1971. (Box 92)
    - Congress, Congressional District
      - General. (Box 92)
      - Information re Vernon, Cudahy, South Gate, and Huntington Park. (Box 92)
      - Maps of California Congressional Districts. (Box 92)
    - Courts, Federal and State. (Box 92)
    - Crime and Criminals
      - General Correspondence. (Box 92)
      - Law Enforcement, Confrontation Between Police and Students. (Box 92)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 92)
      - Organizations. (Box 92)
      - President's Committee on Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Crime (PCJD). (Box 92)
      - School Violence, Juvenile Delinquency. (Box 92)
    - Defense Department, Naval Junior Reserve Officers, Training Corp. (NJROTC). (Box 92)
    - Economy, National
      - Black Economics. (Box 92)
      - The Nixon Economic Record. (Box 92)
      - Small Business, Bubble-Up Corporation. (Box 92)
      - Small Business Administration, CANDO (Community and National Development Operations Services Corporation). (Box 92)
      - SBA, Earthquake Loans. (Box 92)
      - SBA Loans. (Box 92)
      - Small Business, Woods Systems, Incorporated, Contractor/Construction. (Box 92)
      - Unemployment. (Box 92)
      - Unemployment (Full Employment). (Box 92)
      - Unemployment and Full Employment Clippings. (Box 92)
      - Newsclippings, Miscellaneous. (Box 92)
    - Education
      - All Win - U.S.A., Los Angeles County. (Box 92)
      - Black Education Commission. (Box 92)
      - Busing, School. (Box 92)
      - Culture. (Box 92)
      - Elementary and Secondary, Urban Affairs, New Opportunity Development (NOD). (Box 92)
      - Free Community University. (Box 92)
      - Grants/Funds. (Box 92)
      - Higher Education. (Box 92)
      - Higher Education Task Force. (Box 92)
      - MARC (Minority Access to Research Centers). (Box 92)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 92)
      - Mexican-American Education Commission. (Box 92)
      - National Institute of Education. (Box 92)
      - National Policy Conference on Education for Blacks,, Washington, D.C., March 1972 (Box 92)
      - Newsclippings, etc. (Box 92)
      - Office of Educational Programs. (Box 92)
      - Overseas Education Association, Incorporated. (Box 92)
      - Pre-School. (Box 92)
      - Right to Read. (Box 92)
      - Schools, Los Angeles City. (Box 92)
      - SW Regional Lab for Educational Research and Development (SWRL). (Box 92)
      - Vocational. (Box 92)
    - Energy, Newsclippings and Misc. (Box 92)
    - Federal Government, Home Rule for D.C. (Box 92)
    - Foreign Relations
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous. (Box 92)
      - Greek Prisoner, Alexandros Panagoulis. (Box 92)
      - Newsclippings. (Box 92)
      - Tiger Cages, South Vietnam Prisons on Conson Island. (Box 92)
    - Health
      - Central City Community Mental Health Center. (Box 93)
      - Child Care Centers. (Box 93)
      - Drew Postgrad. Medical School, A Mental Health Study of the Aged in Inner City. (Box 93)
      - Kedrin Community Health Center. (Box 93)
      - Medicare and Medicaid. (Box 93)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Hospital. (Box 93)
      - MEDEX Program, Drew Medical School. (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Newsclippings. (Box 93)
      - National Institute of Child Health and Human Development. (Box 93)
      - South Central Multi-Purpose Health Services Center. (Box 93)
      - Watts Community Hospital. (Box 93)
      - Watts Extended Health and Family Planning Group. (Box 93)
      - Watts Extended Health, Incorporated HMO. (Box 93)
      - John Wesley County Hospital. (Box 93)
    - Hearings
      - Headstart Equal Opportunity Act of, 1964, May 1971. (Box 93)
      - Legal Services for the Poor, May 1971. (Box 93)
      - Summer Youth Programs and Neighborhood Youth Corps, April 1971. (Box 93)
      - Education in the 1970s, March 1970. (Box 93)
      - Manpower Programs, April 1970. (Box 93)
      - Anti-Poverty, August 1965. (Box 93)